# TALAY CHATISUT

# SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# **KEY COMPETENCIES**

- Project management skills
- Agile development methodologies
- Communication skills
- Teamwork
- Creative thinking
- Problem solving

## **SKILLS**

#### Blockchain

- Rust, Solidity
- NFT, DeFi, DEX, Smart Contract

# Web Frontend

- React, Angular, Vue.js
- HTML5, CSS3, ES6+, Typescript

# Web Backend

- Laravel, CodeIgnitor, Symfony
- Node.js, Express.js, Nest.js
- Ruby on Rails
- Django, Flask
- ASP.NET

#### Mobile

- React Native, Flutter, Ionic
- Kotlin, Java, Swift

## Database

- MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite
- MongoDB, GraphQL
- Firebase, AWSRDS

# **CONTACT INFO**

170/33 Sukhaphibal 1 Road Klongkum,

Bangkok, 10240, Thailand

Email: lamskills113@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/lamapps

Phone: +66 662 3787387

## PERSONAL SUMMARY

Creative software engineer with 8+ years of experience. As a talented and hardworking developer, I always stick to a resultdriven working manner with great attention to detail, periodic thorough code review, and critical thinking.

The best quality, accurate timeline, free and polite after-service are what I guarantee to my clients.

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Remote 10/2020- Present

Refinable is a decentralized multi-chain NFT marketplace for users to trade items from across the metaverse. Discover, Trade, and Create NFTs from the best and upcoming projects and collections on Ethereum, Solana, Binance Smart Chain, and Polygon.

- Built the first biggest NFT Marketplace of digital art on Binance Smart Chain using ERC-721 for single and ERC-1155 for multi NFT and BEP-20 for governance token.
- Developed whole smart contracts from scratch and past the Audit from SlowMist.
- Built token bridge between Binnance and Ethereum so that users are able to migrate their NFTs from ETH to our platform.
- Implemented basic functionalities of NFT marketplace such as sale, auction, airdrop and used proxy for service fee calculation.
- Implemented NFT fractionalization so that users are able to co-won NFT and decide further steps like sale, auction, airdrop together.
- Developed on-chain & off-chain governance protocol with FINE token so that users are able to tomake decision of adding new features and modifying current functionalities of platform.

Key Achievements: NFT Sale, Airdrop, Service Fee, Auction, NFT Fractionalize, NFT Bridge, Governance

## **PROJECT MANAGER**

DelifreshEU Company 04/2021- 09/2021 https://shopee.getmoresell.com

Built the Shopee product sale boosting site based on Thailand with Shopee API integration and GB Prime payment gateway integration.

- Use the robust structure of Laravel PHP framework and Vue.js for elegant and flexible UX/UI design.
- Provide CI/CD and solid infrastructure for maintaining and updating continuously, Landing page's loading speed optimization, SEO friendly, perfect accessibility and separate dashboard codebase from landing page and use subdomain for dashboard codebase so that provide highly performance and security.
- Shopee product boosting / bumping service without clicking "boost" button in every 20 minutes manually, this sites' goal is Automatic boosting and bumping service by using Shopee open API.
- Supporting 3 kind of payment method: Credit/Debit Card, QR Code, TrueMoney wallet.

# ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Bachelor of Computer Science Chulalongkorn University, Malaysia 2009 - 2013 (4 years)

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

# Certificate of Completion

Udemy

2020

This is to certify that Vue Long successfully completed 80 hours of Node with React:
Fullstack Web Development online course on
Dec 15, 2020

#### Graduate

Comsats Institute of information Technology 2013

Graduated as an IT student with excellent academic records throughout.

## WHAT I'M PROUD OF

# My Courage

To always leave my comfort zone. I'm not afraid to do whatever I need to do to achieve my goals!

# My Competitive Effort

I can't stand to be behind of someone and like to be in front of him.

# My Focus & Persistence

Despite any hard situation, I keep my focus on my goals and always move towards them.

## Keeping Good Relationship

I like to be a right-hand man regarding all the aspects.

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Kinect Card Limited 05/2017 ~ 11/2017 https://www.kinectcard.com/

My role was senior frontend developer and I achieved to make an elegant and fully responsible Pixel-Perfect UX/UI design by using React/Next.js

- Made a lot of component for modularity, router and redux optimization.
- · Reduce the bundle file size for high page loading speed.
- Using strict test tools like Jest to ensure correctness of JavaScript codebase.

#### SENIOR RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER

Remote | 01/2018 - 02/2018

Integration new function for CRM to Chatwoot open source project. Fat-Free CRM functions integrated into chatwoot by using Ruby on Rails,

PostgreSQL, Redis and Vue framework.

- Integration API for Vue frontend
- Convert Fat-Free CRM UI to Vue UI,
- Customization of Openproject
- Create Live Chatting room via WebRTC(video, voice and file share function)

#### MOBILE APP DEVELOPER

ADDonation Organization | 04/2019- 09/2019 | https://addonation.org

ADDonation.org is a not for profit organization supporting varieties of nonprofit organizations around the world. (e.g. environmental, saving children, animal protection)

- Support both Android and iOS mobile app using React Native Expo (SDK 42)
- Firebase FireStore and Realtime Database, OAuth2.0
- Advertisement video streaming service using expo AV video
- Schedule notification
- Nest.js, React for admin panel and website.

# SENIOR ASP.NET DEVELOPER

LiveNetVideo.com | 01/2020 - 08/2021 | https://livenetvideo.com

This project's goal is making a video meeting app using ASP.NET SignalR

- Real-time communication with SignalR and WebRTC
- Able to create a meeting and invite any online user
- High video and audio quality communication
- ASP.NET core 5 and Angular 12
- Ionic 5 for mobile version

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Dentinizer App | 02/2019 - 08/2019 | https://wcods.com/

Dental Site based on United State

- Laravel 8 for backend and Vue.js for frontend
- Odoo integration for Invoice, transactions and financial staff
- Vuexy theme customization
- · Several kinds of user role management, doctor, patient, nurse, recipient

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Multi Vendor Marketing Company | 2013- 2014https://supplieson.com

Tensail Analytics provides clients with unprecedented gaming industry expertise combined with a comprehensive customerfocused vision. The combination of the two is unmatched within the gaming service provider marketplace.

- Scraped details of sports events, odds, boxscores, match stats, leaderboards from espn, rivals, synergy, stats-ncaa, donbest, pgatour and more.
- Analysed the data contents and made expectation for the future match results.
- Provided expectations with several formats according to the license Kept managing the unmanaged.
- VPS server